<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string-array name="quotes">
<item>Give, and it shall be given to you. For whatever measure you deal out to others, it will be dealt to you in return.</item>
<item>Love is patient; love is kind
and envies no one.
Love is never boastful, nor conceited, nor rude;
never selfish, not quick to take offense.
There is nothing love cannot face;
there is no limit to its faith,
its hope, and endurance.
In a word, there are three things
that last forever: faith, hope, and love;
but the greatest of them all is love.</item>
<item>Work hard and become a leader; be lazy and never succeed. (Proverbs 12:24)</item>
<item>Be strong and of a good courage, fear not, nor be afraid...for the Lord thy God, he it is that doth go with thee; he will not fail thee, nor forsake thee.</item>
<item>Weeping may endure for a night, but joy cometh in the morning. (Psalms 30:5)</item>
<item>It is easier for a camel to go through the eye of a needle, than for a rich man to enter the kingdom of God</item>
<item>A fool shows his annoyance at once, but a prudent man overlooks an insult</item>
<item>Work hard and become a leader; be lazy and never succeed. (Proverbs 12:24)</item>
<item>For the Lamb which is in the midst of the throne shall feed them, and shall lead them unto living fountains of waters: and God shall wipe away all tears from their eyes.</item>
<item>He only is my rock and my salvation: he is my defense; I shall not be moved.</item>
</string-array>

<string-array name="fonts">
<item>Default</item>
<item>Serif</item>
<item>Monospace</item>
<item>Sans</item>
</string-array>

<string-array name="font_values">
<item>1</item>
<item>2</item>
<item>3</item>
<item>4</item>
</string-array>

<string-array name="text_colors">
<item>White</item>
<item>Black</item>
<item>Red</item>
<item>Blue</item>
<item>Yellow</item>
<item>Green</item>
<item>Purple</item>
</string-array>

<string-array name="text_color_values">
<item>7f070005</item>
<item>7f070006</item>
<item>7f070007</item>
<item>7f070008</item>
<item>7f07000a</item>
<item>7f070009</item>
<item>7f07000b</item>
</string-array>

<string-array name="background_colors">
<item>White</item>
<item>Black</item>
</string-array>

<string-array name="background_colors_values">
<item>1</item>
<item>2</item>
</string-array>
</resources>
